We see what we want to see
Blind is a drama, romance film directed by Michael Mailer.
A novelist is blinded in a car crash that killed his wife and several years later rediscovers his passion for
life and writing when he embarks on an affair with the neglected wife of an indicted businessman.
Bill Oakland, played by Alec Baldwin.
Suzanne Dutchman, played by Demi Moore.
Gavin O'Connor, played by Steven Prescod.
Ella, played by Eden Epstein.
Mark Dutchman, played by Dylan McDermott.
Howard Cunningham, played by James McCaffrey.
Blind is a 2016 American drama film directed by Michael Mailer, written by John Buffalo Mailer, and
starring Alec Baldwin, Demi Moore, Viva Bianca, Dylan McDermott, and James McCaffrey.
The film was released on July 14, 2017, by Vertical Entertainment.
The tone is emotional.